import { Question } from "@/types/Question";

export const questionsByWeek: { [week: string]: Question[] } = {
  week1: [
    {
      question: "Which of the following statements is true?",
      options: [
        "Having extensive knowledge for future leaders is enough",
        "Future leaders only need to be skilled in the 21st century",
        "21st century future leaders should strive to have spiritual wisdom",
        "21st century future leaders need to be in politics",
      ],
      answer:
        "21st century future leaders should strive to have spiritual wisdom",
    },
    {
      question: "To be a leader, one needs a specific official rank or status.",
      options: ["True", "False"],
      answer: "False",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following statements is false?",
      options: [
        "The central concept of leadership is influence",
        "Management is linked directly to a formal position and the authority that comes with it",
        "The leadership process is intentional",
        "Management and leadership are one and the same thing",
      ],
      answer: "Management and leadership are one and the same thing",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Educational leadership is the 2nd most important factor next to ___",
      options: [
        "teachers’ salaries",
        "students’ learning",
        "students’ attendance",
        "teachers’ health",
      ],
      answer: "students’ learning",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The previous focus in the context of education and leadership has been on ___",
      options: [
        "instructional leadership",
        "leadership for learning",
        "happiness leadership",
        "leadership for success",
      ],
      answer: "instructional leadership",
    },
    {
      question: "Current aim of educational leadership is to ___",
      options: [
        "produce transformative leaders",
        "build bureaucratic culture as a way of life",
        "focus on financial gains",
        "produce managers",
      ],
      answer: "produce transformative leaders",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is an existing issue currently in educational leadership?",
      options: [
        "providing a status driven vision",
        "seeking funding agencies",
        "getting infrastructural support",
        "managing staff relationships",
      ],
      answer: "managing staff relationships",
    },
    {
      question:
        "One of the challenges being faced in educational leadership is the tension in being the ___",
      options: ["teacher", "admin", "change agent", "business agent"],
      answer: "change agent",
    },
    {
      question:
        "___ based training approaches often miss the key dimensions of leadership and hence need to include capabilities denoting a dynamic capacity.",
      options: ["power", "competency", "diversity", "personality"],
      answer: "competency",
    },
    {
      question: "The PRES model is a model of ___.",
      options: [
        "charismatic leadership",
        "authoritative leadership",
        "authentic leadership",
        "bureaucratic leadership",
      ],
      answer: "authentic leadership",
    },
  ],
  week2: [
    {
      question: "Professional Development ___.",
      options: [
        "is a static process",
        "spans throughout one’s career",
        "is independent of the work environment & role‐perception relationship",
        "does not cater to the phase of retirement",
      ],
      answer: "spans throughout one’s career",
    },
    {
      question: "CPD should focus on ___.",
      options: [
        "conferences and seminars",
        "guided and formal learning",
        "only activities catering to work",
        "salaries",
      ],
      answer: "conferences and seminars",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Professional Education is concerned with 3 main aspects of development. Which of the following is not one of them?",
      options: [
        "Professional knowledge base",
        "Development of reflection, a critical awareness of the context of their practice",
        "Competence in professional action",
        "Family development",
      ],
      answer: "Family development",
    },
    {
      question:
        "CPD is needed because of the need for development in areas like ___.",
      options: [
        "transferable skills",
        "effective management",
        "assessment",
        "all of the given",
      ],
      answer: "all of the given",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The continuum of needs navigates between ___ needs and personal needs.",
      options: ["national", "international", "cultural", "institutional"],
      answer: "institutional",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is true for 21st century learners?",
      options: [
        "They are networkers and communicators",
        "They lack tech savviness",
        "They are rigid and stagnant",
        "They ignore the various forms of media",
      ],
      answer: "They are networkers and communicators",
    },
    {
      question: "Faculty members throughout their careers should ___.",
      options: [
        "never go back to being students again",
        "focus extensively only on academics while research can be ignored",
        "focus extensively only on research while teaching can be ignored",
        "continuously relearn from experiences",
      ],
      answer: "continuously relearn from experiences",
    },
    {
      question: "A 21st century educator acts as a ___.",
      options: ["mentor", "referee", "moderator", "all of the given"],
      answer: "all of the given",
    },
    {
      question: "Dewey’s “How We Think” gives a five-stage model of ___.",
      options: [
        "Creative Thinking",
        "Reflective Thinking",
        "Emotional Intelligence",
        "Spiritual Thinking",
      ],
      answer: "Reflective Thinking",
    },
    {
      question: "___ theory is given by David Kolb.",
      options: [
        "Constructivism",
        "Experiential learning",
        "Johari window",
        "Reflective practice",
      ],
      answer: "Experiential learning",
    },
  ],
  week3: [
    {
      question:
        "Professional ethics in education are a set of dignified principles put into practice by the ___.",
      options: [
        "teachers",
        "administrative staff",
        "education ministers",
        "students",
      ],
      answer: "teachers",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is a core value of the teaching profession according to the General Teaching Council of Northern Ireland?",
      options: ["Discipline", "Anger management", "Tolerance", "Obedience"],
      answer: "Tolerance",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is true about the code of professional practice?",
      options: [
        "should be updated once in 20 years",
        "should be updated based on interests of the ruling political party",
        "should be obligatory for every student as a public servant",
        "should be updated based on changing societal needs",
      ],
      answer: "should be updated based on changing societal needs",
    },
    {
      question: "Each teacher has an obligation to ___.",
      options: [
        "Exercise leadership in their role as supervisors",
        "Protect students from harm & unfairness",
        "Act with probity in their daily work activities and decision – making",
        "All of the given",
      ],
      answer: "All of the given",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Teachers should not divert from their goals and hence avoid contributing to discussions on review and revisions of policies.",
      options: ["True", "False"],
      answer: "False",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Academic fraud and illegal fees for admission highlight the issue of ___ in the education and teaching sector.",
      options: [
        "privatization",
        "absenteeism",
        "corruption",
        "outdated teacher education curriculum",
      ],
      answer: "corruption",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is not an aspect of political interference as an ethical challenge in the realm of education today?",
      options: [
        "favoritism",
        "low quality teaching",
        "nepotism",
        "transfer misconduct",
      ],
      answer: "low quality teaching",
    },
    {
      question: "The code of ethics ___.",
      options: [
        "should be treated as a living document with wide applications",
        "is intended to be difficult to follow",
        "is a social tool to solve social dilemmas",
        "is present for only the profession of teaching",
      ],
      answer: "should be treated as a living document with wide applications",
    },
    {
      question: "The process of ethical teaching should ___.",
      options: [
        "continue for 7 years",
        "begin from pre-service studentship",
        "begin with the first government job",
        "end 5 years before retirement",
      ],
      answer: "begin from pre-service studentship",
    },
    {
      question:
        "According to the Australian Education and Training Department, Canberra in 2006, the teachers’ Code of Professional Practice is to be based on ___ principles.",
      options: ["four", "seven", "five", "three"],
      answer: "five",
    },
  ],
  week4: [
    {
      question:
        "According to the ability model, emotional intelligence consists of ___ abilities.",
      options: ["five", "four", "three", "seven"],
      answer: "four",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The ability model considers emotions as sources of ___ which help individuals respond appropriately to the social context.",
      options: ["information", "inspiration", "happiness", "social security"],
      answer: "information",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The ability of ___ refers to the ability to detect & read emotions in self.",
      options: [
        "managing emotions",
        "understanding emotions",
        "using emotions",
        "perceiving emotions",
      ],
      answer: "perceiving emotions",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Daniel Goleman has given the ___ model of emotional intelligence?",
      options: ["ability", "mixed", "leadership", "personality"],
      answer: "mixed",
    },
    {
      question:
        "___ is the ability to put oneself in others’ shoes and understand their emotions.",
      options: [
        "Emotional regulation",
        "Self-awareness",
        "Emotional labor",
        "Empathy",
      ],
      answer: "Empathy",
    },
    {
      question: "___ leadership style demands compliance.",
      options: ["affiliative", "democratic", "coercive", "coaching"],
      answer: "coercive",
    },
    {
      question: "‘Come with me’ is the message given by ___ leadership style.",
      options: ["coaching", "authoritative", "democratic", "affiliative"],
      answer: "authoritative",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Idealized influence and intellectual stimulation are intelligence traits of ___ leadership.",
      options: ["transformational", "emotional", "social", "transactional"],
      answer: "transformational",
    },
    {
      question:
        "There are two types of emotional regulation, ___ focused and ___ focused.",
      options: [
        "deep, surface",
        "sympathy, empathy",
        "antecedent, response",
        "process, outcome",
      ],
      answer: "antecedent, response",
    },
    {
      question:
        "___ is a process by which emotions are shared across a group in a social context.",
      options: [
        "Emotional regulation",
        "Emotional labour",
        "Emotional contagion",
        "Emotional intelligence",
      ],
      answer: "Emotional contagion",
    },
  ],
  week5: [
    {
      question: "Which of the following is true regarding goals for diversity?",
      options: [
        "Freedom from ethnocentric stereotypes or biases by educational leaders",
        "Achieving a skewed and biased profile of staff & students",
        "Gender balance to be avoided",
        "Leaders’ commitment to equity",
      ],
      answer:
        "Freedom from ethnocentric stereotypes or biases by educational leaders",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is a dimension of cultural awareness?",
      options: [
        "Masculinity and femininity values",
        "Uncertainty avoidance",
        "Long term or short term orientations",
        "All of the given",
      ],
      answer: "All of the given",
    },
    {
      question: "There are two types of diversity: ___ and ___.",
      options: [
        "structural and interactional",
        "societal and institutional",
        "infrastructural and informational",
        "structural and functional",
      ],
      answer: "structural and interactional",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The impact of each type of diversity is complementary to & enhanced by the presence of the others.",
      options: ["True", "False"],
      answer: "True",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Three major categories of engagements such as citizenship engagements, cultural engagement & compatibility of difference characterize ___ outcomes.",
      options: ["learning", "social", "individual", "democracy"],
      answer: "democracy",
    },
    {
      question:
        "___ outcomes measure aspects like the students’ satisfaction and perception of campus climate.",
      options: ["wellbeing", "cultural", "process", "value"],
      answer: "process",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Colleges & universities now-a-days are struggling with new changing forces. Which of the following is one of them?",
      options: [
        "confronting younger & techno-savvy as well as older & career-driven students",
        "unprecedented competition in the job market",
        "accountability, & affordability in the global context",
        "all of the given",
      ],
      answer: "all of the given",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Growing trends and transformations like virtual universities are a result of ___.",
      options: [
        "globalization",
        "privatization",
        "institutionalization",
        "none of the given",
      ],
      answer: "globalization",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following statements is not true?",
      options: [
        "The per capita increase in state funding has triggered a pressure for universities & technical education institutes to generate new sources of income",
        "Many countries are visualizing the rapid expansion of higher education as the key to their transition of status from developing to developed nations",
        "Considerable variation among the countries on the extent to which funding for higher education & research comes from government, charitable or business sources",
        "Due to the dramatic rise in aspiration & participation in higher education, increased pressure has been created on funding of higher education institutions",
      ],
      answer:
        "The per capita increase in state funding has triggered a pressure for universities & technical education institutes to generate new sources of income",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is not one of the components of the Five point Framework for policy & practice of Inclusion?",
      options: ["Content", "Finance", "Staffing", "Infrastructure"],
      answer: "Finance",
    },
  ],
  week6: [
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is not one of the reasons for the question of ‘why educational research’?",
      options: [
        "Intuitive thinking",
        "Accountability",
        "Development",
        "Effectiveness",
      ],
      answer: "Intuitive thinking",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is not one of the purposes of educational research?",
      options: ["emotional", "descriptive", "explanatory", "evaluation"],
      answer: "emotional",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following statements is true?",
      options: [
        "Correlation means causation",
        "Causal research objective is to determine how a process is taking place",
        "Causal research is the most superior type of research",
        "Proving causality is difficult in social science and hence focuses on probability of occurrence",
      ],
      answer:
        "Proving causality is difficult in social science and hence focuses on probability of occurrence",
    },
    {
      question: "To establish a causal relationship,",
      options: [
        "A clear rationale should be present to study the variables",
        "cause must have occurred after the effect",
        "changes in the value of independent variable must be accompanied by the changes in the value of confounding variable",
        "it must be established that there is another explanation for the change in dependent variable in addition to the causal factor being studied",
      ],
      answer: "A clear rationale should be present to study the variables",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not true regarding a problem?",
      options: [
        "The problem should state a relation between variables",
        "The problem variables should be operationally defined & feasible",
        "A scientific problem should contain implications for testing",
        "Problem should be stated in an ambiguous form",
      ],
      answer: "Problem should be stated in an ambiguous form",
    },
    {
      question: "Action research is important because it ___.",
      options: [
        "Promotes reflective/innovative teaching",
        "Verifies what methods work",
        "Enables teachers to become change agents",
        "All of the given",
      ],
      answer: "All of the given",
    },
    {
      question: "The following factors affect doctoral research, except ___.",
      options: [
        "Political intervention & funding sources",
        "Employer demands",
        "Prioritization of the parents’ experience",
        "Massification of higher education",
      ],
      answer: "Prioritization of the parents’ experience",
    },
    {
      question:
        "___ a continuous process of unlearning, learning, relearning, reflection & evaluation.",
      options: [
        "Conservational pedagogy",
        "Continuous pedagogy",
        "Consequential pedagogy",
        "Critical pedagogy",
      ],
      answer: "Critical pedagogy",
    },
    {
      question:
        "New pedagogies require students to create new knowledge & connect it to the world by using the power of ___.",
      options: [
        "political ideologies",
        "cultural practices",
        "spiritual wisdom",
        "digital tools",
      ],
      answer: "digital tools",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not a deep learning goal?",
      options: [
        "Engage systems in collective effort to mobilize deep learning",
        "Capture & cultivate old pedagogies that hamper deep learning",
        "Identify deep learning work",
        "Operationalize, refine & validate measures for deep learning",
      ],
      answer: "Capture & cultivate old pedagogies that hamper deep learning",
    },
  ],
  week7: [
    {
      question:
        "The 21st Century’s knowledge-based economy & knowledge society need to bring transformational innovation in education through the following except ___.",
      options: [
        "21st century’s skill-based curricula",
        "innovative assessment tools",
        "techno-based & learner centered pedagogy",
        "increasing difficulty of entrance tests",
      ],
      answer: "increasing difficulty of entrance tests",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following statements is not true for the new paradigms of education?",
      options: [
        "advocates for 'No child left behind' Act",
        "recommends for personalized learning assistance",
        "aims to make education more authority and administration centric",
        "advocates for quality education to all",
      ],
      answer:
        "aims to make education more authority and administration centric",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The process in which a tutor or facilitator simplifies elements of tasks to make them within reach of learners to bridge their current knowledge to more sophisticated learning stage is called ___.",
      options: [
        "Scaffolding",
        "Metacognition",
        "Self-regulated learning",
        "Intuitive learning",
      ],
      answer: "Scaffolding",
    },
    {
      question: "Metacognition occurs ___.",
      options: [
        "before the cognitive event",
        "after the cognitive event",
        "along with the cognitive event",
        "can occur before, after or along the cognitive event",
      ],
      answer: "can occur before, after or along the cognitive event",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Under the principles for designing cognitive apprenticeship environments, ___ method refers to the one where teacher enables students to compare their performance with others.",
      options: ["exploration", "coaching", "modeling", "reflection"],
      answer: "reflection",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Under the principles for designing cognitive apprenticeship environments, ___ aspect of content refers to the general approaches for directing one’s solution process.",
      options: [
        "domain knowledge",
        "heuristic strategies",
        "learning strategies",
        "control strategies",
      ],
      answer: "control strategies",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following statements is not true for experiential learning?",
      options: [
        "can be based on both real work and life experiences",
        "does not apply to soft skills",
        "can be based on structured experiences that simulate or approximate real life",
        "can be used for all domains",
      ],
      answer: "does not apply to soft skills",
    },
    {
      question:
        "___ is the extent to which team members’ personal benefits & costs depend on successful goal attainment by other members.",
      options: [
        "Outcome interdependence",
        "Group potency",
        "Constructive conflict",
        "Psychological safety",
      ],
      answer: "Outcome interdependence",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Problem based learning processes stimulate students’ intrinsic interest in the subject matter through various components. Which of the following is not one of them?",
      options: [
        "Theory building",
        "Cumulative reasoning",
        "Recall of information",
        "Cognitive conflicts leading to conceptual rigidity",
      ],
      answer: "Cognitive conflicts leading to conceptual rigidity",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following statements is not true for Mobile-assisted Seamless Learning?",
      options: [
        "It is cross time & locations",
        "It encompasses only the digital world and not the physical world",
        "There is a ubiquitous access to learning resources",
        "It combines the use of multiple device types like tablets and phones",
      ],
      answer:
        "It encompasses only the digital world and not the physical world",
    },
  ],
  week8: [
    {
      question: "Choose the statement that is not true",
      options: [
        "Effective leadership decides more than it demonstrates",
        "Leadership is about motivating people to work together",
        "Leadership is about energizing team members to make good decisions",
        "Effective leadership connects more than it controls",
      ],
      answer: "Effective leadership decides more than it demonstrates",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Turnaround leaders actively invite people to join & identify with the ___ framework to move ahead.",
      options: [
        "steered ability",
        "steered intelligence",
        "steered engagement",
        "steered control",
      ],
      answer: "steered engagement",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is a characteristic of turnaround leaders?",
      options: [
        "They listen with a 'menu' of what has been done elsewhere to successfully address the focus area for improvement",
        "They reach out to those who will make a desired change",
        "They listen carefully to the protestors and aim to remove roadblocks",
        "All of the given",
      ],
      answer: "All of the given",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Turnaround leaders take three critical roles. Which of the following is not one of them?",
      options: ["Role model", "Teacher", "Learner", "Bestfriend"],
      answer: "Bestfriend",
    },
    {
      question:
        "___ leadership works best in higher education as it models what effective teachers do to help students learn.",
      options: [
        "Bureaucratic",
        "Authoritarian",
        "Laissez-faire",
        "Collaborative",
      ],
      answer: "Collaborative",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following capabilities is not a given dimension of the 'Turnaround Academic Leadership Capability Framework'?",
      options: ["Personal", "Interpersonal", "Cognitive", "Spiritual"],
      answer: "Spiritual",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Educational Entrepreneurship has 3 crucial roles. Which of the following is one of them?",
      options: ["Co-opetitions", "Politicians", "Family", "Beaurocrat"],
      answer: "Co-opetitions",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is not a sub-domain of knowledge in the 'Entrepreneurship Competencies Model'?",
      options: [
        "Self-insight",
        "Perseverance",
        "Declarative knowledge",
        "Mental models",
      ],
      answer: "Perseverance",
    },
    {
      question: "___ refers to the self-belief in one’s capabilities.",
      options: [
        "Self compassion",
        "Perseverance",
        "Gratitude",
        "Self-efficacy",
      ],
      answer: "Self-efficacy",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Self-discipline, self-regulation, tenacity, and delayed gratification all highlight ___ in the Academic Entrepreneurship-cum-Performance Model.",
      options: [
        "Academic perseverance",
        "Social skills",
        "Learning strategies",
        "Classroom context",
      ],
      answer: "Academic perseverance",
    },
  ],
  week9: [
    {
      question: "Which of the following statements is true?",
      options: [
        "Education reflects only the present",
        "Education only anticipates the future",
        "Education only reflects the past",
        "Education both reflects what is now and anticipates what is next",
      ],
      answer:
        "Education both reflects what is now and anticipates what is next",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The ___ approach is a combination of synchronous and asynchronous teaching and learning modality.",
      options: ["mixed", "synthetic", "synchronized", "blended"],
      answer: "blended",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Students learning at their own pace in different times and spaces is ___ learning.",
      options: ["Blended", "Synchronous", "Focused", "Asynchronous"],
      answer: "Asynchronous",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Learning outcomes in the form of ___ are the major measures of the teaching and learning in basic education.",
      options: ["knowledge", "skills", "attitudes", "all of the given"],
      answer: "all of the given",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following was not a teacher’s role in the new normal?",
      options: [
        "should be available online at all times to address the queries",
        "must ignore students who choose to not participate",
        "must initiate virtual learning activities",
        "must focus on customized problem solving based on individual needs",
      ],
      answer: "must ignore students who choose to not participate",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The 3Cs in the context of pedagogy for the new normal includes the following dimensions except ___.",
      options: ["consistency", "community", "creativity", "competition"],
      answer: "competition",
    },
    {
      question: "___ is a state of being absorbed in a task.",
      options: ["flow", "exploration", "drain", "optimism"],
      answer: "flow",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is not a phase of the 5E framework of online flipped classes?",
      options: ["explore", "explain", "elaborate", "excite"],
      answer: "excite",
    },
    {
      question:
        "___ is an approach to teaching and learning that creates feedback which is then used to improve students’ performance.",
      options: [
        "Assessment for learning",
        "Action for learning",
        "Feedback for learning",
        "Attention for learning",
      ],
      answer: "Assessment for learning",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is not a characteristic of summative assessment?",
      options: [
        "Highly specific and individual",
        "Highly structured and rigid",
        "Knowledge and comprehension learning is emphasized",
        "Conducted after instruction",
      ],
      answer: "Highly specific and individual",
    },
  ],
  week10: [
    {
      question:
        "Pedagogy means the understanding of the science and practice of ___.",
      options: [
        "children learning",
        "adult learning",
        "women learning",
        "men learning",
      ],
      answer: "children learning",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The term ‘andragogy’ is most closely associated with___, an educator who had a massive impact on the field.",
      options: ["John Watson", "Piaget", "Vygotsky", "Malcolm Knowles"],
      answer: "Malcolm Knowles",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is not one of the seven principles of andragogy?",
      options: ["mentorship", "self-direction", "motivation", "memory"],
      answer: "memory",
    },
    {
      question:
        "According to Andragogy’s principles, transformation means that students are ___.",
      options: [
        "having an open mind about new ideas and perspectives",
        "empowered and responsible for their learning outcomes",
        "encouraged to take part in meaningful experiences outside of traditional classroom settings",
        "encouraged to adapt their learning styles and approach in order to meet the needs of a particular course or program",
      ],
      answer:
        "encouraged to adapt their learning styles and approach in order to meet the needs of a particular course or program",
    },
    {
      question:
        "___ theory states that adult learning is all about making practical sense of learning experiences.",
      options: [
        "Experiential learning",
        "Constructivist",
        "Behavioral reinforcement",
        "Cognitive",
      ],
      answer: "Experiential learning",
    },
    {
      question: "The solution for the learning need of knowledge is ___.",
      options: [
        "transferable skills",
        "learner-analytics",
        "just-in-time learning",
        "social learning environment",
      ],
      answer: "just-in-time learning",
    },
    {
      question: "The best micro-learning content is ___.",
      options: [
        "of 20 minutes",
        "focused on 4-5 concepts",
        "of 9-10 minutes",
        "less than 6 minutes",
      ],
      answer: "less than 6 minutes",
    },
    {
      question: "___ refers to our desire to be self-directed.",
      options: ["autonomy", "mastery", "purpose", "perseverance"],
      answer: "autonomy",
    },
    {
      question: "Heutagogy is also called___.",
      options: [
        "self-determined learning",
        "self-focused learning",
        "self-efficacy learning",
        "self-growth learning",
      ],
      answer: "self-determined learning",
    },
    {
      question:
        "In ___ learning, students do more than think deeply about a problem and their actions to solve it; they reflect on the problem-solving process.",
      options: ["lifelong", "continuing", "double-loop", "single-loop"],
      answer: "double-loop",
    },
  ],
  week11: [
    {
      question:
        "NEP 2020 is an attempt to bring out ___ in educators and learners.",
      options: ["self-restraint", "reflexivity", "self-efficacy", "criticism"],
      answer: "reflexivity",
    },
    {
      question:
        "NEP 2020 is taking various steps to fulfill its goals by focusing on ___.",
      options: [
        "why to learn",
        "when to learn",
        "who should learn",
        "how to learn",
      ],
      answer: "how to learn",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The New education policy recommended a new structure of ___ for school education.",
      options: ["5+2+4+2", "5+3+2+4", "5+3+3+4", "5+3+3+3"],
      answer: "5+3+3+4",
    },
    {
      question:
        "All undergraduate and postgraduate admissions of public HEIs are based on NTA scores conducted at the national level.",
      options: ["CFA", "CBSE", "AICTE", "NTA"],
      answer: "NTA",
    },
    {
      question:
        "According to NEP 2020, undergraduate programs are of four years with a provision to exit after one year with a ___.",
      options: [
        "diploma",
        "advanced diploma",
        "pass degree",
        "project based degree",
      ],
      answer: "diploma",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Four years of Bachelor degree holders can now directly admit to Ph.D. program without Masters degree.",
      options: ["True", "False"],
      answer: "True",
    },
    {
      question:
        "One of the fundamental principles of NEP 2020 is a ___ regulatory framework.",
      options: [
        "light but tight",
        "light but not tight",
        "fast and heavy",
        "heavy but slow",
      ],
      answer: "light but tight",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is not a fundamental principle of NEP 2020?",
      options: [
        "full equity and inclusion as the cornerstone of all educational decisions",
        "facilitation of true philanthropic participation",
        "a rootedness and pride in India and its rich culture",
        "promoting monolingualism and the power of language in teaching and learning",
      ],
      answer:
        "promoting monolingualism and the power of language in teaching and learning",
    },
    {
      question:
        "___ education is a philosophy of higher education that integrates introspection and experiential learning into academic study.",
      options: ["Conducive", "Competitive", "Contemplative", "Constructive"],
      answer: "Contemplative",
    },
    {
      question:
        "___ is the ability to navigate and shift in a healthy way one’s thoughts, emotions, and behaviors in order to make decisions and reach goals that benefit oneself and others.",
      options: ["self-efficacy", "self-insight", "flow", "self-management"],
      answer: "self-management",
    },
  ],
  week12: [
    {
      question:
        "The Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs) were adopted by all United Nations Member States in 2015 as a universal call to action to end poverty, protect the planet and ensure that all people enjoy peace and prosperity by ___.",
      options: ["2030", "2020", "2025", "2023"],
      answer: "2030",
    },
    {
      question: "There are ___ number of SDGs.",
      options: ["17", "15", "20", "13"],
      answer: "17",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Sustainable development was the solution to the problems of environmental degradation discussed by the ___ in the 1987 report *Our Common Future*.",
      options: [
        "Millennium Commission",
        "International Commission",
        "United Nations Commission",
        "Brundtland Commission",
      ],
      answer: "Brundtland Commission",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Poverty can be defined as a lack of ___ which renders it impossible or challenging for human beings to live with dignity and provide for themselves.",
      options: [
        "only money",
        "only vital resources",
        "neither money nor vital resources",
        "money and/or vital resources",
      ],
      answer: "money and/or vital resources",
    },
    {
      question:
        "___ is an alarm signal sent by the body when the stomach is empty and the blood sugar level decreases.",
      options: ["Nutrition", "Nourishment", "Hunger", "Malnutrition"],
      answer: "Hunger",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is not one of the steps being taken or aimed at to fulfill SDG goal 2?",
      options: [
        "promoting sustainable agriculture",
        "supporting small-scale farmers",
        "international cooperation to ensure investment in infrastructure and technology",
        "promoting use of pesticides and insecticides for crop increase",
      ],
      answer: "promoting use of pesticides and insecticides for crop increase",
    },
    {
      question: "SDG Goal 5 concerns with ___.",
      options: [
        "zero hunger",
        "gender equality",
        "clean water and sanitation",
        "affordable and clean energy",
      ],
      answer: "gender equality",
    },
    {
      question: "Safe and affordable drinking water for all requires we ___.",
      options: [
        "harvest in adequate infrastructure",
        "provide sanitation facilities",
        "encourage hygiene",
        "all of the given",
      ],
      answer: "all of the given",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The rapid growth of cities is a result of rising population and ___.",
      options: [
        "increasing migration",
        "increasing emigration",
        "increasing global warming",
        "increasing literacy",
      ],
      answer: "increasing migration",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is not a core competency of sustainability leadership?",
      options: [
        "systems thinking",
        "social innovation",
        "sustainability literacy",
        "passive values",
      ],
      answer: "passive values",
    },
  ],
};
